[{"answer": "Excuse me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "She had references", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't live near here, ya know! my friend, my friend and my friend are at my friend's apartment", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "So she's giving me the massage and I'm just making conversation", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Neither do I, but I do it for them. I figure they're bored", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well so she mentioned that she had a son, and the for some reason I launch into the story about the kid from that place who was abducted", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes, it was", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Not if you have a doctor's note", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Not if you have a doctor's note", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Well I've never actually done it but if I really wanted to I could probably get one from my friend my friend, the dentist", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, I don't want the man either", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He'd just be touching your back", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What's the difference, you're a woman. They're supposed to be touching you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He'd just be touching your back too", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He'd just be touching your back too", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I know. That's the point. If it's gonna get sexual, it should get sexual with you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I wouldn't be comfortable", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What could happen", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What could happen", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It's supposed to feel good", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What if it felt good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't want it to feel good", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I said, 'What do you do?'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You don't know what you do", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "How did you hurt this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You don't know", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "But you just told m", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You hurt it in that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What's with you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yes, A...", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes, A...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yes, a man gave you...", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "A man gave me..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "A man gave me... a massage", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "So he... had his hands and, uh, he was..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He was... touching and rubbing", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "That's a massage", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You took your pants off", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Moved", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Moved", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I'm sure it didn't move", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "It may have moved, I don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "It moved! It was imperceptible but I felt it", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Okay, so what if it moved", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "That's not the test. Contact is the test, if it moves as a result of contact", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I just saw my friend in Dinky Donuts. You know, I looked in there and there he was having coffee and a donut", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yeah. my friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I can't see my friend sitting at the counter in little tiny filthy smelly Dinky Donuts", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "He can have a donut, but not at Dinky", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "He didn't say he can't", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "He doesn't feel funny", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I mean, if you feel funny about it at all", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "If he does", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "He doesn't feel funny", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Do you feel funny? He didn't say anything", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "If he does", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "He feels funny. You don't have to do this", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "How would I know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "What do you mean, like him", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Do you like him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Do you like him", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "What do you mean, like him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I mean he's a good fighter and a nice guy but I don't like him", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "I told you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I told you we shouldn't do it", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Told me what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "He didn't say anything", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Why'd you do that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Of course I was getting you a note", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "I just thought maybe I could talk to my friend. my friend walks in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Hi my friend", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well it's not tragic", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "No, it's..", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Okay. I mean, what if th", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "I'm not happy", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "I mean I'm happy sometimes, but not now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Note.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Yeah, college was fun. my friend walks in again and interjects", "qsentId": 82}]